https://nagutierrez-cl.vercel.app

NICOLAS GUTIERREZ LEPICHEO

FULL-STACK WEB DEVELOPER

1 year of experience working as a front-end developer with ReactJs. Knowledge to do back-end support tasks with NodeJs, using Sql and No-Sql databases.

Ability to analyze and solve customer problems with the initiative to propose new ideas and solutions.

Experience

Front-End Developer

May 2022 - Now | Andes Industrial

- In charge of the front-end development of the company's projects, defining designs, technologies and libraries.
- Development of the company's new e-commerce, taking an existing project and making architectural changes, reducing the number of API calls and component renderings, as well as taking new requirements.

Technologies used:

Html, Css, Sass, Javascript ES6, ReactJs, NextJs, Bootstrap, Ant Design, Material UI, reCaptcha, react-router

Freelance Full-Stack Project

November 2021 - January 2022 | Nexxo S.A.

- A solution was designed and implemented for the HR department of a local company, working with personal data of employees and applicants.
- The hiring process, which is in high demand at times of the year, was facilitated thanks to the solution provided.

Technologies used:

Html, Css, Javascript ES6, ReactJs, ReduxJs, Bootstrap, NodeJs, ExpressJs, MongoDB, Mongoose, JsonWebToken

IT Support Internship

June 2019 - October 2019 | Nexxo S.A.

• Troubleshooting in the IT area for the company's employees, maintenance, preparation and assignment of equipment.

Education

Técnico de Nivel Superior en Computación e Informática April 2020 | Universidad de Magallanes

Certifications

EFSET English Certificate 78/100 (C2 Proficient)

July 2022 | EF Standard English Test (EF SET)

Contact

Email

na.gutierrez@outlook.com

City

Punta Arenas, Chile

Phone

+56 9 90802146

Technologies

JavaScript ES6

ReactJS

ReduxJS

NextJS - Vercel

Material UI

Ant Design

CSS - SASS

Bootstrap

NodeJS

ExpressJS

Restful API

Http status codes

JsonWebToken

Sql Server - MySql

MongoDB - Mongoose

GitHub

Postman

Jira

Skills

Fast learner

Agile methodologies

Problem solving

Teamwork